

Aganith Shanbhag

Education

BTech In Electronics and Communication CGPA:9.13/10

MANIPAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, MANIPAL 2019-PRESENT

Higher Secondary

12TH GRADE PERCENTAGE- 92.0

10TH GRADE CGPA- 9.4

LITTLE ROCK INDIAN SCHOOL. BRAHMAVAR 2004-2019

Skills

C++

PYTHON

WEB DEV

VERILOG HDL

SPICE

Profile

An Electronics Engineering student with an interest in Software Engineering. I love Web Development and currently learning App Dev. Recent projects include React and React-native with Firebase BaaS. I am experienced with C++, Python, Matlab, Pspice, Naspice, Proteus and have spent a considerable amount of time on Arduino Projects.

Work Experience

ASME Manipal Student Chapter

MANAGEMENT COMMITTEE

AUG 2020 - PRESENT

- Designed and constructed the electronic circuit of a 3D printed Drone for IAM3D Competition
- Developed electronic systems and prototypes for competitions like 'Line follower Bot'
- Trained the Working Committee to write SEO friendly Web articles
- Scheduled major aspects of meeting for the Working and Management Committee developed solutions for Workshops and Webinars every week

Major Projects

SCIENTIA WEEKLY

SEPT 2020 - PRESENT

- · Developed the website, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery coding.
- Facilitated day-to-day running of Content on the Website, ensuring high levels of productivity and progression.
- Formulated a small team of 4 Content Writers and Web Developers for further development.

COWIN-SLOT-FINDER

JUN 2021

- Built a Cowin slot finder application using ReactJS which requests the Public Cowin API for JSON Data
- Made use of Firebase as BaaS for Authentication



